Richard Ahn

RICKY@ONEHOUSE.IO • 562-453-9564 SAN FRANCISCO, CA

Profile

I've worked with various startups and clients at a web consultant firm for the past 5 years. One of my responsibilities was to have a thorough understanding of each product we would be building and offer support to clients and users to help troubleshoot bugs.

WORK EXPERIENCE

RA POWER MANAGEMENT | FRONT-END DEVELOPER | JUL 2016 -

2017

Met with clients and discussed product specifications and goals. Real Time troubleshooting bugs on the system on a production level. Developed and designed UI for their backend application implementing graphic charts to show data by using chartkick.js.

Ygrene | FRONT-END DEVELOPER | AUG 2014 - 2016

Managed their ticketing system for contractor workflows on Zendesk and dealt personally with issues that would arise from projects. Worked on numerous pages for their financing reports and contractor workflow pages. Also designed and implemented their email templates for notifications when various stages of their projects were completed or needed attention.

IronRidge | FRONT-END ENGINEER | AUG 2013 - 2016

Met personally with their design team and spoke directly with them when any issues arose on their website. Implemented Salesforce integration to their front end and dealt with tickets for potential customer leads. Setup and tracked Google Analytics for the application. Front-end development and integration with Rails backend. Worked with their design team to create landing pages and product description.

SKILL SETS

- Zendesk
- Salesforce
- Microsoft Word/Excel/Powerpoint
- Google Analytics
- Photoshop
- Responsive HTML5
- BEM/CSS3 via Sass
- JQuery
- Content Management Systems (Wix, Wordpress, Squarespace, Weebly,)
- Ruby on Rails
- Github

Education

California State Polytechnic University, Pomona

Bachelor Degree in Psychology | 2012 - 2014

Mt. San Antonio College

2010 - 2012